<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">kosICT-STIKK</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="aboutconf">KosICT is a Regional Conference organized by STIKK (Kosovo Association of Information and Communications Technology) and each year intends to cover the global trending tropics of ICT by gathering international, regional and local speakers.In addition, during this event the Kosovo ICT Association- STIKK will celebrate its 5th anniversary</string>
    <string name="speakers">Speakers</string>
    <string name="sponsors">Sponsors&amp;speakers</string>
    <string name="about">About the conference</string>
    <string name="AndersIndset">Anders, the born Norwegian out of Trondheim is serial-entrepreneur, management-thinker and speaker in the fields of leadership, branding and innovation. Anders offers companies a different mindset for creative solutions, change and sustainable growth. In 2004 he founded the creative agency evoworkx media in Bad Neustadt an der Saale together along with his partner with the goal to offer companies creative marketing solution on a fullservice scale. Amongst the clients are numerous SMB companies and so called „hidden champions“ and also DAXCompanies such as LINDE Group and Deutsche Post DHL. Over the years Anders has initiated several start-ups from cloud-based software tools, eCommerce applications to an online printhouse (DRUCKHELDEN.DE which he co-founded and build before selling the shares in 2010). Anders is founding partner and managing director of LWL GmbH - Leaders We Love, a company seated in Frankfurt am Main, which have specialized on premium C-Level executive education. LWL GmbH host and run the Marketing &amp; Innovation Forum Europe in Frankfurt and the Manager Meeting Europe also in Frankfurt, to which yearly on each forum 500 top-manager gather to discuss current changes and trends and to get inspiration from the leading global experts and the makers and leaders around the world.</string>
    <string name="update_app">Do you want to check for updates?\n\n If updates are found, you will have to re-install the app manually.</string>
    <string name="AridLarsen">Arild Bjørn-Larsen holds an MBA and has extensive management experience in the fields mark branding, strategic development, digitization and the Internet. Bjørn-Larsen has experience from companies such as Apple, NetCom, Norligruppen, JBR / McCann Multimedia, Spray GK / Razorfish and Tarantula. He leads Booksellers Association Digitization Committee and a competency project run by BI, where 16 large Norwegian companies develop strategic competence in the use of Internet and mobile services.</string>
    <string name="BernardJanischowsky">Bernhard Janischowsky is co-founder and COO of Trestle Group. He has enjoyed a truly global professional career, having begun as an Industrial Engineer in Dallas, Texas. Thereafter, he moved to Spain to join the German engineering group Bosch International, where he was directly responsible for transferring manufacturing processes between locations. He then moved into consulting, advising on the reengineering of corporate strategy of former East German state-owned conglomerates. He was later recruited into Arthur Andersen Business Consulting in Frankfurt, Germany to manage a variety of international projects in the areas of process design and IT strategy. After five years with Arthur Andersen he and three partners founded ecovista, a company focused on planning and implementing large scale IT projects for international clients. Building upon this success, Bernhard co-founded Trestle Group and as COO is responsible for all project delivery. Bernhard holds a degree as Industrial Engineer from the University Erlangen-Nuernberg in Germany and an M.B.A. from London Business School.</string>
    <string name="JimmyLeach">Jimmy Leach is a digital consultant working for a number of international clients dealing with digital transformation, including the internet governance organisationICANN, the Dubia-based Gems Education and the crowd-funding publisher Unbound. He also advises clients on similar matters for the public relations and public affairs company Portland Communications.
								Prior to all this, he was Head of Digital Diplomacy for the UK\'s Foreign and Commonwealth Office which in turn followed stints as Editorial Director for Digital at The Independent newspaper; director for digital at Freud Communications; Head of Digital Communications for Prime Ministers Blair and Brown in Downing Street and executive editor at Guardian.co.uk.
								He lives in south London</string>

</resources>
